[{"answer": "Don't need to think fast to handle beer", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I told her all my relatives are goo", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What's weird about that", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Guess I'm not like most women", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I'm just quiet", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Neither do you", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "So... what's your dark secret", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Don't you think I should know before we have sex", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Good. That's an honest answer. And why don't you like coming here", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Is it just my cheery personality that makes your skin itch", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Maybe it's the way I look. Or the sound of my name", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Because if you did, I know a therapist named my friend. I also know a therapist named my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "my friend? I don't have a problem with that", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I don't need someone else", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " So, what did you do", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Molested little girls", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Fucking Tigers. They got no pitching except for a bunch of green kids straight out of Double A or Southern Cal.  How was the party", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "The birthday party", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I don't feel anything. ", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "She was born after they put me away. How can I have feelings", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "She was born after they put me away. How can I have feelings", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Have to talk about something", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Do you think you're crazy", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Why do you think you're here", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Will I ever be normal", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You couldn't say", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Is it their innocence? Their beauty?..", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "They seduce you", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I have no idea", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Why don't you just tell me", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What did you think would happen", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "What did you want to happen? ", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'm not scared. ", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Maybe you should be", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "That's my answer", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Nothing. Can I open my eyes", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I don't see", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " When the two of you held each other. When you were ten or eleven and she was eight or nine. When your parents were out and the two of you were alone... completely alone in that big house", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "All right. A small house... with small rooms", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " I'm not a monster", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Maybe I'm not a good man. Maybe inside I'm bad, and I'll always be bad", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Sneak up behind me like that", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Why's it always my fucking problem", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Sure you do. He cuts open the wolf's stomach, and the girl steps out alive", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "That's it. Little Red Riding Hood jumps out of the wolf's guts with hardly a scratch.  Ever see a seve", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Your daddy will always love you", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I know because... it's just something I know", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": " Time", "docId": "Woodsman_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "I feel... okay", "qsentId": 54}]